Guide to the Robert College records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Faculty Lists
  - Myers, Jane Ellen (Box 16)
  - Myers, Walter F., Jr. (Box 16)
  - Nadolsky, Alexandre S. (Box 16)
  - Nalle, Beauveau B. (Box 16)
  - Nash, Nancy E. (Box 16)
  - Nash, Ralph S. (Box 16)
  - Nath, Laurence A. (Box 16)
  - Nebioglu, Hope B. (NEBI) (Box 16)
  - Nebioglu, Orhan (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Carl L. (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Dennis (RCCS) (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Hazel L. (Box 16)
  - Newell, Arthur F. (Box 16)
  - Nadi, Mary Elizabeth (Box 16)
  - Nadler, Joseph R. (Box 16)
  - Newman, William H. (Box 16)
  - Nichols, Ethel C. (Box 16)
  - Nichols, Terry W. (Box 16)
  - Nickle, Harry (Box 16)
  - Nigar, Nigar (Box 16)
  - Nilson, May E. (Box 16)
  - Nilson, Paul (Box 16)
  - Nisco, Elizabeth (Box 16)
  - Noack, Sigrid (Box 16)
  - Noblitt, Isabelle (Box 16)
  - Nollie, Kenneth J. (Box 16)
  - Nolte, Harriet (Box 16)
  - Nolte, William (Box 16)
  - Nordhus, Phillip B. (Box 16)
  - Nowicki, Anna (Box 16)
  - Nowicki, Przemyslaw (Box 16)
  - Noyan, Kemal (Box 16)
  - Noyce, Gaylord B. (Box 16)
  - Lay, Chester F. (Box 17)
  - Layton, William S. (Box 17)
  - Leaton, Anne (Box 17)
  - Leavitt, John H. (Box 17)
  - Lee, Arthur B. (Box 17)
  - Lee, Diana (Box 17)
  - Lee, Stephanie C. (Box 17)
  - Leeming, David A. (Box 17)
  - Lehtinen, Meri K.T. (Box 17)
  - Leigh-Manuell, Herbert C. (Box 17)
  - Leighton, Lisa G. (Box 17)
  - Leinbach, Joseph N. (Box 17)
  - Lerseche, Louis O. (Box 17)
  - Lester-Austin, Michael (Box 17)
  - Lewis, Elizabeth L. (Box 17)
  - Lewis, Geoffrey (Box 17)
  - Lindberg, Evangeline (Box 17)
  - Linder, Fay M. (Box 17)
  - Lindstrom, Wendell D. (Box 17)
  - Linke, Clive (Box 17)
  - Linke, Marion (Box 17)
  - Linton, Norma J. (Box 17)
  - Little, A. John, Jr. (Box 17)
  - Little, Alene S. (Box 17)
  - Little-Olson, Pearl E. (Box 17)
  - Lium, Ester M. (Box 17)
  - Lizer, Katherine E. (Box 17)
  - Lockerby, Florence K. (Box 17)
  - Logan, Ellen J. (Box 17)
  - Love, Nicolette A. (Box 17)
  - Lovelace, Miles (Box 17)
  - Lovett, Carla (RCCS) (Box 17)
  - Lovett, James (Box 17)
  - Lukens, Mary Ann (Box 17)
  - Lyon, Beulah H. (Box 17)
  - Lytle, Dean W. (Box 17)
  - Lytle, Marilyn M.S. (Box 17)
  - MacAlpine, David M. (Box 17)
  - McBeath, Bernard C. (Box 17)
  - McBeth, Thomas J. (Box 17)
  - McCally, Richard K. (Box 17)
  - McCarthy, John P.C. (Box 17)
  - McCauley, Marion M. (Box 17)
  - McCloy, Shelby T. (Box 17)
  - McCreery, Henry F., II (Box 17)
  - McCrodden, Howard J. (Box 17)
  - McCrodden, Kathyrn (Box 17)
  - McDowell, Gary L. (Box 17)
  - McElroy, Carolyn L. (Box 17)
  - McGrady, Mary (Box 17)
  - McKeen, Robert C. (Box 17)
  - McKillop, Marjorie L. (Box 17)
  - McMickle, Gwendolyn (RCCS) (Box 17)
  - McMickle, Robert H. (Box 17)
  - MacGregor, William G. (Box 17)
  - Macinnis, Margaret R. (Box 17)
  - MacKenzie, Rhoda R. (Box 17)
  - Macmillan, Zebulum L. (Box 17)
  - MacNeal, Charles S. (Box 17)
  - MacNeal, Sarah R. (Box 17)
  - Macomber, Hilliard K. (Box 17)
  - Macpherson, John (Box 17)
  - Maevers, Klaus (Box 17)
  - Maggart, Kaye (RCCS) (Box 17)
  - Magnus, David R. (Box 17)
  - Maley, Eileen J. (Box 17)
  - Malinowski, Constance (Box 17)
  - Malone, Jennifer (RCCS) (Box 17)
  - Malter, Henry (Box 17)
  - Manukyan, Arman (Box 17)
  - Marchand, Hans (Box 17)
  - Markhasin, Valery A. (Mr.) (Box 17)
  - Marshall, Paul D. (Box 17)
  - Martin, Candace (Box 17)
  - Martin, Helen U. (Box 17)
  - Mason, Elizabeth (Box 17)
  - Masson, Renee O. (Box 17)
  - Matejka, Kathleen (Box 17)
  - Matejovsky, Catherine (Box 17)
  - Mathews, Joseph J. (Box 17)
  - Matters, Robert L. (Box 17)
  - Maurer, Frank W., Jr. (Box 17)
  - Mavioglu, Joyce E. (Box 17)
  - McGee, Barbara Ruth (Box 17)
  - Meeker, Gesine (Box 17)
  - Mehta, Neil (RCCS) (Box 17)
  - Melton, Robert P. (Box 17)
  - O'Connor, John R. (Box 18)
  - O'Dell, W.H. Sterg (Box 18)
  - Oktay, Necla (Box 18)
  - O'Lauglin, Mildred (Box 18)
  - Oliver, June (Box 18)
  - Olson, Charles R. (Box 18)
  - Onor, Guzey (Box 18)
  - Onur, Idelle E. (Box 18)
  - Ord, Keith (Box 18)
  - Orhon, Alper (Box 18)
  - Orr, John B. (Box 18)
  - Ory, Lucienne (Box 18)
  - Osborn, Helen V. (Box 18)
  - Osmun, Shirley C. (Box 18)
  - Otte, Elizabeth P. (Box 18)
  - Ouellette, Edward F. (Box 18)
  - Ovenden, Alan (Box 18)
  - Ozbal, Hadi (Box 18)
  - Padgett, Lawrence E. (Box 18)
  - Palmer, Jean T. (Box 18)
  - Palmer, Edgar Z. (Box 18)
  - Panarelli, Joseph E. (Box 18)
  - Parker, David J. (Box 18)
  - Parker, Thomas W. (Box 18)
  - Parquette, William S. (Box 18)
  - Parrish, Daniel L. (Box 18)
  - Parsons, Carolyn (Box 18)
  - Pate, Glen (Box 18)
  - Pate, Wiley G. (Box 18)
  - Paulin, Ruth N. (Box 18)
  - Pearce, Katharine S. (Box 18)
  - Pearson, J. Raymond (Box 18)
  - Pearson, Thomas A. (Box 18)
  - Peet, Louise J. (Box 18)
  - Pektas, Juseyin (Box 18)
  - Pelletier, Lois (Box 18)
  - Pelisinger, Ronald (Box 18)
  - Pescud, Chloe (RCCS) (Box 18)
  - Peslikis, Michael (Box 18)
  - Peterson, Samuel R. (Box 18)
  - Pfeifer, H. Peter (Box 18)
  - Pfeifer, Maija L. (Box 18)
  - Pfeiffer, Timothy A. (Box 18)
  - Pickett, Stanley F. (Box 18)
  - Pierce, Martha R. (Box 18)
  - Platzier, John A. (Box 18)
  - Platz, Mabel B. (Box 18)
  - Pliatska, Dorthea (Box 18)
  - Pogirski, Carol (Box 18)
  - Pond, James B. (Box 18)
  - Pond, Jeannette (Box 18)
  - Pope, Thomas K. (Box 18)
  - Porter, David (Box 18)
  - Porter, Scott (Box 18)
  - Ports, Horace G. (Box 18)
  - Post, Bertram (Box 18)
  - Potts, Francis (Box 18)
  - Powell, Donald L. (Box 18)
  - Powers, Helen (Box 18)
  - Premo, Douglas O. (Box 18)
  - Prescott, Edith (Box 18)
  - Price, Joyce (RCCS) (Box 18)
  - Primer, Virginia A. (Box 18)
  - Quaintance, Richard E., Jr. (Box 18)
  - Raby, Stephanie (Box 18)
  - Radcliff, Edward (Box 18)
  - Ralph, Marion (Box 18)
  - Ralph, Philip L. (Box 18)
  - Ramsaur, Ernest E., Jr. (Box 18)
  - Ramsay, Carl (Box 18)
  - Randolph, Stella (Box 18)
  - Rank, Inkeri A. (Box 18)
  - Rawlings, Hoyt (Box 18)
  - Ray, Catherine (RCCS) (Box 18)
  - Ray, Donald (Box 18)
  - Reasoner, Charles F. (Box 18)
  - Redden, Dorothy S. (Box 18)
  - Reed, John T. (Box 18)
  - Reid, Elenor (Box 18)
  - Reid, Richard S. (Box 18)
  - Reigart, Catherine M. (Box 18)
  - Repp, Richard C. (Box 18)
  - Rhasis, Rallou A. (Box 18)
  - Rice, Leonard A. (Box 18)
  - Rich, Francis N. (Box 18)
  - Richards, Alice W. (Box 19)
  - Richards, Marion N. (Box 19)
  - Riefstahl, Rudolf (Box 19)
  - Riffle, Roy E. (Box 19)
  - Rimawi, Walid H. (Box 19)
  - Ring, Martha D. (Box 19)
  - Ring, Priscilla A. (Box 19)
  - Rissman, Bernice S. (Box 19)
  - Ritter, John (Box 19)
  - Robb, Izetta W. (Box 19)
  - Robb, Kevin W. (Box 19)
  - Roberts, Cornelia M. (Box 19)
  - Roberts, Emory G. (Box 19)
  - Robinson, Timothy D. (Box 19)
  - Robinson, M.M.E. (Box 19)
  - Rockwell, John G. (Box 19)
  - Rodd, David B. (Box 19)
  - Roelofs, Irene (Box 19)
  - Rogers, C. Ruth (Box 19)
  - Rogers, Donald W. (Box 19)
  - Rogers, Kay J.P. (Box 19)
  - Rogers, Martin H. (Box 19)
  - Rogers, Mary C. (Box 19)
  - Rogers, Richard (Box 19)
  - Roome, Angela (Box 19)
  - Romig, Eleanor C. (Box 19)
  - Root, Scott E. (Box 19)
  - Rose, Robert & Donna (Box 19)
  - Rosen, Burton R. (Box 19)
  - Ross, Linnea C. (Box 19)
  - Rowell, Judith (Box 19)
  - Rowland, Richard L. (Box 19)
  - Rupp, Beverly (Box 19)
  - Ryan, Mildred E. (Box 19)
  - Ryden, Robert P. (Box 19)
  - Rymph, Raymond C. (Box 19)
  - Sabarth, Mary R. (Box 19)
  - Safoglu, Recep A. (Box 19)
  - Sahin, Kenan (Box 19)
  - Sakarya,Eshref (Box 19)
  - Sakmar, Ismail (Box 19)
  - Salkowski, Peter (Box 19)
  - Saltuk, Ismail (Box 19)
  - Sampey, Jane R. (Box 19)
  - Saraf, Nadya (Box 19)
  - Sarich, Safija (Box 19)
  - Satneck, Walter J. (Box 19)
  - Sayre, Robert F. (Box 19)
  - Scanlon, Helen L. (Box 19)
  - Schaffer, Ruth (Box 19)
  - Schott, Florence N. (Box 19)
  - Schulman, Marcy A. (Box 19)
  - Schur, Barbara A. (Box 19)
  - Seelye, Kate C. (Box 19)
  - Schenck, Cornelius (Box 19)
  - Schereschewsky, John F. (Box 19)
  - Schier, Johanna (Box 19)
  - Schinzinger, Roland (Box 19)
  - Schinzinger, Jane (Box 19)
  - Schlee, Ernest (Box 19)
  - Schneider, Leone K. (Box 19)
  - Schultz, George F. (Box 19)
  - Schultz, Ilse (Box 19)
  - Schuman, Robert P. (Box 19)
  - Schwartz, Dieter F. (Box 19)
  - Scipio, Lynn A. (Box 19)
  - Scott, Eveline A. (Box 19)
  - Scott, Mildred (Box 20)
  - Scott, Richard C. (Box 20)
  - Scott-Thomas, John F. (Box 20)
  - Scribner, Charles H., Jr. (Box 20)
  - Seager, Elizabeth L. (Box 20)
  - Sebuktekin, Hikmet (Box 20)
  - Seely, Jonathan F. (Box 20)
  - Seelye, Laurens H. (Box 20)
  - Segel, Stanley L. (Box 20)
  - Seidelman, Hebert L. (Box 20)
  - Seidler, Lee J. (Box 20)
  - Selis, Elaine (Box 20)
  - Senol, Ahmet (Box 20)
  - Sepe, Rosmarie (Box 20)
  - Sergeant, David (Box 20)
  - Sessa, Virginia (Box 20)
  - Sekvet, Fazile (Box 20)
  - Sekvet, Fazuka (Box 20)
  - Seyman, Rauf (Box 20)
  - Sezer, Mariea (Michels) (Box 20)
  - Shana'a, Mohammed Y. (Box 20)
  - Shana'a, Joyce A. (Box 20)
  - Shaw, Amy I. (Box 20)
  - Shea, Penelope S. (Box 20)
  - Shechner, David (Box 20)
  - Sheehan, Mark (Box 20)
  - Sheeser, John M. (Box 20)
  - Shefer, Viola (Box 20)
  - Sheiry, Edward S. (Box 20)
  - Shelton, Florence C. (Box 20)
  - Shepard, Barclay M. (Box 20)
  - Shepard, Constance (Box 20)
  - Shepard, Martha W. (Box 20)
  - Shepard, Whitman (Box 20)
  - Shermer, Carl L. (Box 20)
  - Sherman, Eleanor J. (Box 20)
  - Shine, Nicholas F., III (Box 20)
  - Shiras, G. Peter (Box 20)
  - Shuey, Rebekah (Box 20)
  - Sibley, Fannie B. (Box 20)
  - Signell, Karl L. (Box 20)
  - Silker, DeWaine C. (Box 20)
  - Sipfle, David A. (Box 20)
  - Sipfle, Mary Alice (Box 20)
  - Sirmna, Nancy G. (Box 20)
  - Skarlatos, Mikhail N.S. (Box 20)
  - Skarlatos, Theresa B. (Box 20)
  - Skinner, Catherine (Box 20)
  - Slater, Anne M. (Box 20)
  - Slater, Louis M. (Box 20)
  - Sleeper, William A. (Box 20)
  - Slotter, R. Arden (Box 20)
  - Smink, Douglas I, Jr. (Box 20)
  - Smith, Alexander (Box 20)
  - Smith, Egida V. (Box 20)
  - Smith, Helen G. (Box 20)
  - Smith, James W., Jr. (Box 20)
  - Smith, Phyllis J. (Box 20)
  - Smith, Rachel L. (Box 20)
  - Smith, Stephen H. (Box 20)
  - Smith, Waldo E. (Box 20)
  - Sogusku, Ann (Box 20)
  - Sohngen, Robert L. (Box 20)
  - Sommer, Claren D. (Box 20)
  - Sommer, Jean M. (Box 20)
  - Soram, Mebruke A. (Box 20)
  - Sorensen, David T. (Box 20)
  - Sorenson, Maude J. (Box 20)
  - Sorensen, Virginia (Box 20)
  - Soyak, Suveyda (Box 20)
  - Spector, Marvin R. (Box 20)
  - Speedie, Ian B. (Box 20)
  - Speedie, Barbara A. (Box 20)
  - Spiegelglas, Stephen (Box 20)
  - Spindel, Jeanette (Box 20)
  - Spindel, Murray (Box 20)
  - Spinos, Efthalia (Box 21)
  - Spooner, Clara M. (Box 21)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth B. (Box 21)
  - Stantus, Daniel J. (Box 21)
  - Starr, Elizabeth (Box 21)
  - Steltzer, William N., Jr. (Box 21)
  - Stene, John K. (Box 21)
  - Stetson, Kirk R. (Box 21)
  - Stevens, Harlan R. (Box 21)
  - Stevens, Jean M. (Box 21)
  - Stevens, Malcolm P. (Box 21)
  - Stevenson, Mary Lillian (Box 21)
  - Stevenson, Nancy K. (Box 21)
  - Stewart, Anne H. (Box 21)
  - Stewart, David C. (Box 21)
  - Stewart, Martha (Box 21)
  - Stewart, Maureen (Box 21)
  - Stewart, Nancy M. (Box 21)
  - Stickney, Edith P. (Box 21)
  - Stilz, Ethel (Box 21)
  - Stivers, Earl R. (Box 21)
  - Stoever, Herman J. (Box 21)
  - Stokes, Edith L. (Box 21)
  - Stokes, Jerome W. (Box 21)
  - Stokes, Gladys A. (Box 21)
  - Stoltzfus, Benjamin (Box 21)
  - Stoltzfus, Esther (Box 21)
  - Stone, Editha (Box 21)
  - Stone, William C. (Box 21)
  - Stotz, Carl L. (Box 21)
  - Stout, May T. (Box 21)
  - Stratton, Arthur M. (Box 21)
  - Strickland, Betty Jo (Box 21)
  - Strommer, Jean T. (Box 21)
  - Stuber, LeRoy (Box 21)
  - Sugg, Robert (Box 21)
  - Sukur, Armenuhl (Box 21)
  - Summers, Nellie (Box 21)
  - Sumner-Boyd, Hilary (Box 21)
  - Surette, Paul V. (Box 21)
  - Surette, Bonnie (Box 21)
  - Sussman, Martin V. (Box 21)
  - Sutherland, C. Hale (Box 21)
  - Suzuki, Peter (Box 21)
  - Swain, Donna M. (Box 21)
  - Swenson, Marcia (Box 21)
  - Swingler, Pervenche (Box 21)
  - Tahmincioglu, Zaharia (Box 21)
  - Talbot, Marian (Box 21)
  - Tanberk, Sibel (Box 21)
  - Tandal, Gillian (Box 21)
  - Tank, Elizabeth (Box 21)
  - Tansever, Mumin (Box 21)
  - Targal, Kamhi (Box 21)
  - Taylor, Sally Anne (Box 21)
  - Teegarden, Joseph (Box 21)
  - Tenerelli, Doreen (Box 21)
  - Templeton, Harry R. (Box 21)
  - Terada, Suki (Box 21)
  - Tharinger, Judith (Box 21)
  - Terry, Henrietta P. (Box 21)
  - Terzi, Karen M. [RCCS] (Box 21)
  - Tezcan, Semih S. (Box 21)
  - Tezel, Akin (Box 21)
  - Thayer, Clark (Box 21)
  - Thayer, Dr. Jacqueline (Box 21)
  - Therriault, Emerson M. (Box 21)
  - Thirkell, Evelyn (Box 21)
  - Thomas, Elizabeth M. (Box 21)
  - Thomas, Lewis V. (Box 21)
  - Thomas, Ethel N. (Box 21)
  - Thomas, Theresa A. (Box 21)
  - Thompson, A. Stanley (Box 21)
  - Thompson, Barbara S. (Box 21)
  - Thompson, Beatrice E. (Box 21)
  - Thompson, Cameron (Box 22)
  - Thompson, Charles W. (Box 22)
  - Thompson, Eveline A. (Box 22)
  - Thompson, Martha (Box 22)
  - Thompson, Mary C. (Box 22)
  - Thornett, Mary (Box 22)
  - Thychsen, Grace (Box 22)
  - Tilley, Edmund (Box 22)
  - Tobey, Harry G. (Box 22)
  - Todd, J. Edward (Box 22)
  - Tolun, Perihan (Box 22)
  - Topaloglu, Mine (Box 22)
  - Tosh, Audrey A. (Box 22)
  - Tosh, Robert W. (Box 22)
  - Totten, Mindy (Box 22)
  - Toven, Baha (Box 22)
  - Townsend, Annis M. (Box 22)
  - Trees, W. Scott (Box 22)
  - Tranter, Barrie (Box 22)
  - Tregillus, Margaret R. (Box 22)
  - Troland, John (Box 22)
  - Trosh, James F.P. (Box 22)
  - Trusk, Ellen M. (Box 22)
  - Trusk, Robert J. (Box 22)
  - Tucker, Cassell C. (Box 22)
  - Tucker, Martha N. (Box 22)
  - Tucker, Phillip N. (Box 22)
  - Tumay, Karen N. (Box 22)
  - Tumay, Mehmet (Box 22)
  - Tuori, Consetta (Box 22)
  - Tupper, S. Alice (Box 22)
  - Turgut, Claudia R. (Box 22)
  - Tursen, Ruhsar (Box 22)
  - Ullyot, Philip (Box 22)
  - Ulmer, Eugene (Box 22)
  - Umur, Aydin (Box 22)
  - Unel, Orvilla G. (Box 22)
  - Unger, Carol E. (Box 22)
  - Ungan, Aydin (Box 22)
  - Unghvari, Charlotte (Box 22)
  - Unkashevich, G.S. (Box 22)
  - Updegraff, Kathryn M. (Box 22)
  - Uzdilek, Salih M. (Box 22)
  - Vande Bunt, Margaret J. (Box 22)
  - Van Der Beets, Richard, Jr. (Box 22)
  - Van Dyke, George E. (Box 22)
  - Van Karssen, Folkert (Box 22)
  - Van Luik, James (Box 22)
  - Van Nice, Elizabeth R. (Box 22)
  - Van Nice, Mary (Box 22)
  - Van Nice, Robert L. (Box 22)
  - Van Vorst, William D. (Box 22)
  - Vautier, Elizabeth (Box 22)
  - Veolitze, Mary (Box 22)
  - Vetter, Jeanette K. (Box 22)
  - Vikasevitch, Yorgi (Box 22)
  - Virtue, Charles (Box 22)
  - Vlasto, Dorothy (Box 22)
  - Voll, Walter C. (Box 22)
  - Von Reinhold-Jameson, James R.P.R. (Box 22)
  - Wadsworth, Lori (Box 22)
  - Widelich, Alfred T. (Box 22)
  - Waite, William W. (Box 22)
  - Walker, Elbridge, Jr. (Box 22)
  - Wallace, Louise B. (Box 22)
  - Wallace, Mary Lee (Box 22)
  - Wallick, Elizabeth A. (Box 22)
  - Walls, Ainslee (Box 22)
  - Walls, Donald (Box 23)
  - Walsh, Dennis M. (Box 23)
  - Walsh, Edwin P. (Box 23)
  - Walsh, Karen E. (Box 23)
  - Walsh, Letty M. (Box 23)
  - Walters, Joanne (Box 23)
  - Walters, Thomas E. (Box 23)
  - Ward, Roscoe F. (Box 23)
  - Ward, Theodore S. (Box 23)
  - Wasosky, Eugene S. (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Walsh, Alleine H. (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Waters, Lyn H. (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Wathen-Dunn, Weiant (Box 23)
  - Watson, Ernest B. (Box 23)
  - Watrous, M. Chilton (Box 23)
  - Watters, Mary Alice (Box 23)
  - Webster, Edward E. (Box 23)
  - Webster, Helen M. (Box 23)
  - Weckman, Christel (Box 23)
  - Weeks, Dr. Rebecca (Box 23)
  - Weinland, Joseph L. (Box 23)
  - Weinrich, John E. (Box 23)
  - Weir, William T. (Box 23)
  - Welch, Charlotte M. (Box 23)
  - Weller, Henry L. (Box 23)
  - Wellington, Catharine M. (Box 23)
  - Wettstein, David (Box 23)
  - White, Helen E. (Box 23)
  - Whitmore, Edward K. (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Williams, George Woods (Box 23)
  - Williams, Phyllis A. (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Alberta Z. (Box 23)
  - Winkler, Barth (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Winterbottom, Christine (Box 23)
  - Wise, Sheldon (Box 23)
  - Wittler, Nancy (RCCS) (Box 23)
  - Wright, Ellen K. (Box 23)
  - Wright, Nancy L. (Box 23)
  - Yalcin, Ali S. (Box 23)
  - Zina, David J. (Box 23)
  - Yenicag, Ayfer (Box 23)
- Series VI: Education Committee
  - Education Committee-General (1973-1988) (Box 23)
  - Education Committee-General (1989-) (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- November 8, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- May 14, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- February 14, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- November 5, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- November 4, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- November 10, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- November 23, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Education Committee- May 14, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee- February 9, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee- February 16, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee- June 15, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee- December 1, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee- November 29, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee Report November 1996 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee Report March 1996 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee Report November1999 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee Report November 1998 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee-February 1998 (Box 24)
  - 8-Year Issue (Box 24)
  - Education Committee-November 1997 (Box 24)
  - Education Committee Report May 1997 (Box 24)
  - The Robert College Story by Herbert H. Lane (Vol. I) (Box 24)
- Series VII: Publications
  - Report of Annual U.S. Giving July 1, 1991-June 30, 1992 (Box 26)
  - Alumni Contributions to 125th Year Book and Art Exhibit May 13-27, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Robert College Annual Giving Report and Honor Roll (1994-2005) (Box 26)
  - Robert College Annual Giving Report and Honor Roll (1992 1990 1989) (Box 26)
  - Middle East Economic Service, (Vol. I Nov & December 1947 Vol. II January 1948) (Box 26)
  - The Near East: A Publication of the Near East Society (1954-1955) (Box 26)
  - Promotional: "Carpet Ride to Turkey" (1980s) (Box 26)
  - "Why Should I Support RC?" (1981-1982) (Box 26)
  - Promotional Booklet (1980) (Box 26)
  - Development Reports (1960-1961) (Box 26)
  - RC-USA Newsletter-Volume 1, July 1990/Volume 1, Number 2, December 1990 (Box 26)
  - RC-USA Newsletter-Volume 2, Number 1, April 1991/Volume 2, Number 2 July 1991/Volume 2, Number 3 December 1991 (Box 26)
  - RC-USA Newsletter-Volume 3, Number 1, April1992/Volume 3, Number, 2 July 1992 (Box 26)
  - RC/Publications-Report of Annual Giving (1979-1980) (Box 26)
  - Trustees Appoint Head and Interim Head of Robert College (1992) (Box 26)
  - American College of Beirut-Syrian Protestant College (forerunner of American College at Sofia) (Box 26)
  - Beirut American University Annual Report (June 1872) (Box 26)
  - Syrian Protestant College (University of Beirut) & RC Brochure (N.Y. Office) (Box 26)